DUOHAN ZHANG

Tel:(+1)6089773453dzhang357@wisc.edu

Department of Statistics, University of Wisconsin Madison

SHORT BIO

Duohan Zhang is currently a master student of data science and statistics in Department of Statistics, University of Wisconsin Madison. He is very fortunate to work on an off-policy reinforcement learning(RL) project with Professor Josiah Hanna. Prior to that, he was a bachelor student in University of Science and Technology of China, majoring in statistics.

EDUCATION

University of Wisconsin Madison

Madison, Wisconsin 2021/9 - 2023/5

Department of Statistics, master in Data Science

GPA: 3.82/4.0

University of Science and Technology of China

Hefei, China 2018/9 - 2022/6

Department of Statistics, bachelor in statistics

GPA: 86.47

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Robust On-Policy Sampling for Data-efficient Policy Evaluation

2021/12 - 2022/5

University of Wisconsin Madison Advisor: Prof. Josiah Hanna

• Submitted paper "Robust On-Policy Sampling for Data-Efficient Policy Evaluation" to NeurIPS under review.

Online forgetting process for moderate linear regression

2021/2 - 2021/8

The university of science and technology of China

Advisor: Prof. Xiao Guo

- Motivated by the EU's "Right To Be Forgotten" regulation, we proposed a moderate dimensional regression in which past data has to be deleted while features are increasing at the same time.
- Proposed a new algorithm solving the problem.
- Unfortunately, we didn't continue to complete this project after I come to United States.

AWARDS

Student scholarship from USTC

2019,2020

School of Management, University of Science and Technology of China

SKILLS

Programming Languages and Tools

Python, Open AI gym, C, R, LaTeX, Mathematica